i've pasted the
error message from this problem into our
text editor so that we can take a look
at it
we need to determine what the problem is
here and which of the four options we've
been presented
is the cause of this problem so the
error is a
no method error reading the error
message
it tells us undefined method keys for
array
this message tells us that we have
invoked the method
keys on an array however this method is
undefined
and if we take a look at the
documentation for the array class
we can see that there is no keys method
the keys method is a hash method and you
can take a look at that in the ruby hash
class documentation invoking the
keys method on a hash will return an
array of all the keys in that hash
so the correct answer to this problem is
option b
there is no method called keys for array
objects
you